Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
- Go on. Duke!
- Punish him. Duke.
Don't get stuck in the corner!
He's The Duke. Duke. Duke!
- Hey!
- Ref!
- You ain't got nothing!
- Ref. come on!
You fuckin' cheatin'!
Fuckin' wanker!
You do that again.
I'll break your fuckin' legs!
Come here you fuckin' prick!
Let's go! Let's fuckin' go!
Oi. Colman!
This how you let your fighters
carry on?
Yeah?
He caught ya. yeah?
He caught ya' 'cause
you're fuckin' about.
Hey. the people came to see
a show. bruv.
And I'm givin''em one.
I say fuck the show.
let's fight fire with fire.
Yo. Jay. would you just
shut up and clean his eye.
I don't want the ref
to call it a stoppage.
Go fuck' em up. mate.
It's good to see the British
press out here supportin' Duke.
He looks off. you reckon the
occasion is too much for him?
No occasion too big
for "The Duke."
I knew that
the day I signed him.
What's important is bringing
that belt back to the UK
and showing the world
that Marshall Promotions
is a major force
in the boxing game.
And what do you say
to allegations
that Marshall Promotions is a
front to launder drug money?
How' 'bout I jam that pen
in your fuckin' ear. mate.
It's okay. son.
Listen.
if you want a private interview.
I can give you one.
just not now.
After the fight.
My team can direct
you to my suite.
Very good.
One more question--
Oh. all right. okay.
Are you out your fuckin' mind?
Never take attention away from
what's happening in the ring.
When are you gonna get that
in your fucking head. eh?
You fuckin' idiot.
Sorry. dad.
How much longer
are you gonna feel him out?
All I need is three rounds.
four tops. then I got him.
I know his rhythm now.
Well then. show them
who they came to see.
The fuckin' Duke.
Yeah?
The only round that matters...
...is the next one.
Come on! Yes!
Go. Duke!
Go on then bruv!
Yes!
Yes. brother!
Out!
Yes!
For the WBC.
heavyweight championship
of the world.
Maduka "The Duke" Kilroy!
Yes!
Whoo!
What's the point
of all this. Walsh?
You could be writin' about...
footballers...
anything...
why this?
Why me?
'Cause you're a phony.
and you hide behind boxing.
Phony?
See. people like you.
they feel they're
so high on their horse.
that they can't fall off.
So then...
we have to knock you off.
Boxing...
is a criminal enterprise.
Always has been.
and always will be.
Tonight's story...
is gonna be about Duke.
And that's it.
Heavyweight fuckin'
champ of the world...
- Can you believe this. Joy?
- Of course I can.
Told you ten years ago
you would.
You used to call me
"The Oracle."
Okay.
Why weren't you there tonight?
I looked at some houses...
Hmm.
LA is nice.
Yeah.
but is it something for us?
It'd be nice for us. yeah.
By the water.
couple of bedrooms.
Everything we always
talked about. and plus.
as a developer
I can begin to sell there.
So what's the hold up?
No hold up.
Joy...
what's the hold up?
Duke. are we really gonna
do this right now?
It's your night...
you're the heavyweight champ.
Yeah...
you're right.
But it's our night.
Just like we said. right?
Tomorrow. life changes.
I talked with Colman.
Everything's in place.
I sign with him.
leave Kingsley.
and we move to LA.
We set our own path.
It's easy for you to say.
You can now do
whatever you want.
Hey...
where I go. we go.
I love you.
I always have.
and I always will.
Ever since we
were kids at school.
So let me hear you say it.
Hmm?
Tomorrow.
we will start our new life.
Duke...
I need to hear you say it.
Tomorrow.
we start our new life.
Mmm.
I gotta go.
It's the champ!
All right. make a speech bruv.
Hey. everyone shut the fuck up!
The champ wants to speak!
- Yeah!
- Whoo!
My head hurts too
much to have a sip.
so you all have three for me.
yeah?
Uh...
Joe Lewis.
Ali.
Frazier.
Foreman.
Holmes.
Tyson.
Holyfield.
Seven of the greatest
heavyweights of all time.
but what's the
common denominator...
Not one of them was from London.
But Duke...
- Duke's gonna change that.
- Come with me.
He's gonna show the world
that the greatest
doesn't have to be American.
That the greatest can.
and will be from London.
Let's raise a glass
to "The Duke."
You're not only
London's favorite son...
you're like a son to me.
Hmm.
Now go and enjoy the expensive
food and drink I'm paying for.
I could fit the yard I grew up
in in Jamaica inside this room.
Everything I built
from the ground up.
Never took a handout
from nobody.
I not only earned this...
I deserve it.
Yeah. you come a long way.
Loving family. beautiful wife.
your daughter
expanding the business.
You got everything you need. right?
Well. men like you and me.
we're not...
we're not measured
by wives and children.
We're measured by what we build
with our own two hands.
That's what lasts forever.
Congratulations.
Oh. damn. wow...
a hug and congratulations
from CeCe.
I'm winning everything tonight. wow.
- See ya.
- Mmhmm.
I saw you talking
to the investors.
- Get you a drink?
- Please.
Everything on top?
Numbers look good.
Really good. actually.
We start the necessary
paperwork now.
could be on track
to breaking ground
on the second casino
within the year.
Half a dozen across Europe
in the next five.
Yeah. maybe down the road.
But right now. we need to ride
this wave that Duke is on.
About the office
space for your wife...
Her name's Joy.
I'm not sure now
is the best time for a...
vanity purchase. if you ask me.
Wasn't asking.
- You good?
- Yeah. yeah. yeah...
Do you think Dad was
watching the fight?
I don't know. man.
But what I do know...
...is I see you.
my not so little brother.
I couldn't have gotten
here without you. you know.
- Well. you did all the work.
- Shut up. man.
Don't be so humble now. man.
come on.
All right. it was all me.
Thank you. man. I love you.
I love you too.
Where's Jay? You seen him?
No.
I'll go check him in his room.
- All right.
- Meet you at the car park.
All right.
Man of the hour. yeah?
Hey.
Congratulations. fam.
Listen. I booked out the
entire Tao nightclub for us.
Baddies. bottle service.
everything's padded bruv.
Uh... I appreciate it. Z. but um.
me. Jay and Cal gonna have
a low key one at Aria.
When I'm back in London.
we can. uh. we'll meet up.
Have a proper celebration.
all right?
Yeah. all good.
Calvin!?
Cal?!
Yo. Jay?!
Yo!
Ah!
Get him!
Get his hands!
Get his fucking hands!
Do it!
Get him!
Duke!
Ah!
Calvin!
Calvin...
Cal...
Stay with me man.
stay with me.
Duke...
Calvin...
Calvin!
Call the police!
Ah!!!
Police!
Make space!
Freeze!
Put your hands in the air
and do not move!
Do not move!
My name is Amado Rodriguez.
I am a man of great influence...
which allows me and my people
a level of access to any
and everything we need.
But on occasion.
I like to use my influence
to grant someone else
something they need.
I don't need anything from you.
Except to be left alone.
I beg to differ. English.
You need desperately
what I can give you.
Yeah?
And what's that?
A reason to live.
Get the fuck off me.
Get off me. man!
We were just meant to break
your hands. that's all.
We didn't mean for
your brother to--
Why?!
You were fucking
Kingsley Marshall's wife.
I gather simple revenge would
suffice in this situation.
but something tells me that
won't be enough for you.
because it's not revenge
you're after...
it's a reckoning.
I help you find Kingsley
and get revenge.
In return. I take over
the London drug market.
It starts now.
If you do this. English.
there's no turning back.
Kilroy.
It's a going away gift.
from Amado.
Fuckin' hell!
How'd you know
I was landing today?
What. you think
I wouldn't know?
Fuck off. come here.
- All right?
- Yeah. man.
Yeah. You all right?
Got a present for ya.
Oh. man.
Shit. I ain't had these
in ages. man.
Now. is that good?
Yeah. it's good.
So. where you
workin' these days?
Well. I do freelance debt
collection around the city.
What's that mean?
Come on...
You know. when people don't
pay what they owe. then I...
well. I go around and
I- and I politely...
remind them to do so.
I heard Kingsley's
done a runner.
No one's seen
or heard from him in months.
You hear anything?
Hear all sorts of rumors.
Everything from he's in hiding.
'cause the old bill
building up a case against him.
to he's in Turkey gettin'
his hairline fitted.
You know the one that
Lewis Hamilton went to?
What do you think?
Guy drives a racecar.
what the fuck do
I care about his hairline?
Come on.
Why didn't you respond
to any of my letters or calls
over the last eight years?
I didn't respond to anybody.
Yeah. I should have been
there that night. Duke.
Shit. bruv. there is not
a day that goes past
that I don't feel guilty.
you have no idea.
Yeah. but I do...
'cause I was there.
Yeah...
let's get you inside. yeah?
Use your jab. Keep him away
from you. Keep moving.
Who told you all you could stop?
Come on!
Two minutes left on the
timer boys. come on.
What's the number
one rule in my gym?
Uh...
um...
no food allowed in the gym.
What's the number one rule?
No visitors allowed
without you knowin'.
No visitors without me knowing.
I don't even
know why I'm here. man.
Come. let's go.
I'll stay with you.
No. actually. sorry bruv.
I'm on my old lady's
sofa at the moment. So...
you can't sleep on the streets.
I mean. Gazzer won't let ya.
Yo. speak for yourself
young man. yeah?
Talk to me. What you need?
Just a spot to lay my head.
Fuck off. mate.
Does that mean the family's
back together then. yeah?
Jay...
just fuck off.
Got it. okay. Sure.
It's like. father-son thing.
I got- yup. fuckin' off.
You good?
Keep workin' boys. yeah?
You need a spot?
Here.
That's all I got.
A sign come for ya.
Sí.
27 Mill Lane.
- You ready for stage one?
- I'm headin' to the gym now.
Gentlemen. welcome to the
home of London boxing.
Behind every great boxer
is a great promoter.
And behind every great promoter.
is something even bigger.
Something deeper.
And that's where you find the
true heart of this game.
What greases the wheels
and makes it roll.
To win big.
you've got to be prepared
to do whatever it takes.
Cross whatever line.
It's hard work.
You've got to face brutality.
Shit can be scary. bruv.
It can reveal your
darkest nightmares.
And that's where you find out
what this game is all about.
How far you're willin' to go.
When it's rollin'...
Whoo!
It can gift you rewards
beyond your wildest dreams.
So. the only question you
have to ask yourself is...
how much you want to win.
Welcome to the Marshall family.
First question please.
Albert Cross. UK Boxing Online.
Abisov is fifteen
without a loss.
do you think you can handle
his power
and become
World Heavyweight Champion?
This motherfucker punches
with fuckin' pillows.
Jackhammer's 12-0.
12 K.O.'s.
forget that clown.
I'm the bloody guv'nor'!
Hey! Hey! Hey!
It's gon' be first round.
That's all it takes
to get this guy down.
that's all it takes...
Maduka?
CeCe...
Wow. look at you.
It's Cebella.
Not CeCe.
I was born here.
I'm as British as
King Charles. nigga.
Let's go. let's go. let's go.
This place is...
massive.
- Come a long way.
- We have.
Though. not without our share
of hurdles along the way.
Yeah. yeah.
I heard about your dad.
Um...
I hope everything's all right.
He's fine.
Just away on business.
So...
why you here. Duke?
You wanna fight again?
No. No. my fightin'
days are behind me.
But I was thinkin' maybe
I could work for you and Zeek.
I just...
help train some of the
young pups. you know?
So. silence for years.
and then you show up here
and ask for a job?
I know how it looks--
No. I don't think you do.
What happened to Calvin
was a tragedy.
But what you did after...
how you did it.
The media storm you left
for my father to clean up...
nearly destroyed him.
and our business.
That's why I wanted to
come back and fix things.
Anyway I can.
After I put you to sleep.
your girl's gonna be wide awake
celebratin' the real champ.
I'm gonna slap that booty.
What you gonna do?
- I'm gonna slap that booty.
- Oh. shit.
Simeon. don't just stand there.
Get the girls on.
O-ok cuz. sorry. Sorry.
Ladies. let's go. let's go.
Duke!
As I live and breathe.
Hey. you're not back with
the Marshalls are you?
No comment. Albert.
But that shouldn't stop you
asking the question.
Maduka Kilroy's just
been released from prison.
is it true he's coming to work
for Marshall Promotions?
Who told you that?
Yeah. that's right.
You heard it here first.
"The Duke" is back where he
belongs at Marshall Promotions.
I know you're new to all this.
but the press is here
to promote our fight.
not Duke Kilroy.
If this circus is what I'm
to expect while you in charge.
maybe it's not time
for our fight to happen.
- We have a contract.
- I have a contract...
with Kingsley. not you.
Now. you may look the part.
doesn't mean that
you can fill his shoes.
Let's bounce.
Zeek. relax bro.
No. nah. nah...
- Hey.
- There he is.
- Hey man.
- Duke motherfuckin' Kilroy!
The champ in the flesh- oh...
former...
Mmhmm.
Kinda stole my
shine back there. yo.
Wasn't my intention for
things to turn that way. man.
But listen. I'm a fan. yeah.
And if there's ever any advice
or tips I can pass along.
please.
No. no. Jackhammer
don't need no tips.
- Right.
- This is lightwork for me. baby.
Zeek.
I'ma holler at you later.
Champ!
Oh...
former.
Your boys got confidence.
I give him that.
You got a lot of nerve
showin' up like this.
That little stunt you pulled
may have gotten you
through the door.
but it's only 'cause I say so.
You work for me.
I got it.
Whatever you say.
We've got an open
sparring session tomorrow.
We'll see what you got.
I'll be there.
Du-ke!
Go!
Oh. fuck.
Go. go. go. go!
How bad's your arm?
I'm fine. Let's go.
Sí. jefe.
Duke.
- Hey.
- English!
Life on the outside looks
good on you. my brother.
Dime. how things are
progressing with your role?
Yeah. there was some initial
reluctance
from CeCe and Zeek
about me being back in the fold.
but I'll be able
to work around it.
Bien.
And the operation?
Plan's set.
Tomorrow night.
we plant the drugs
at a Russian owned warehouse.
then call in a tip to the cops.
Drugs get seized.
the Marshalls blame the
Russians for stealing them.
and a very bloody
internal war starts.
One that Kingsley will be forced
out of his hole to stop
or risk losing
his entire business.
And I'll take it from there.
You can obviously see
it's such an amazing property.
Wonderfully located as well
in central London--
Excuse me.
do you do rentals?
Um. uh...
take your time. think about it.
give me a ring.
we'll talk numbers. yeah?
- Have a great day.
- Thank you.
Thought you were gonna hit me.
Wow. this...
this place is amazing. Joy.
- I'm proud of you.
- Two hundred and fourteen.
That's how many times
I tried to reach you.
Joy...
I'm sorry.
I didn't talk to anyone.
Duke. I wasn't just anyone.
I want to see you again.
Come on. Out of the car.
- All right. I'm comin'.
- Come on. slow poke.
Sorry. Mrs. Marshall.
I thought your viewings
were over.
- You said eleven.
- Hi mum.
It's not a problem. Langston.
We're done.
What's goin' on.
little man? You good?
Yeah. Who are you?
Uh. I'm a friend of your mums.
Yeah. we grew up together.
My name's Duke.
I'm Aiden.
Nice to meet you.
You too.
L-Langston. I'll be out
in a second. yeah?
Go. go with Langston.
Look. Duke...
I gotta go.
Okay.
Here's another look at the CCTV.
It looks like they
got one of 'em.
Lot of fuckin' good that did.
Something funny to you?
No. boss.
Huh?
The fuck you laughin' at?
Funny now. huh?
Zeek...
Fucking mixed breed.
So. this is all we've got. hmm?
Some grainy video
and a generic white van
that half the people
around here use?
Simeon. I thought you were
supposed to replace the cameras
around the front?
Sorry. I...
Oh.
Just wait outside.
I don't know why you keep
that fuckin' idiot around.
We just lost three point five
million quids worth of product.
Every member of our network
is gonna be losin' money.
Yeah...
but what if one of those
members is responsible?
Whoever did this had to know
when the shipment was
comin' in.
And when and where to hit it.
Okay.
The only way to know for sure...
is to look each one of them
in the eye and see who blinks.
He relies too much on his speed.
Leaves himself
open all the time.
You're gonna have
to work on his defense.
His footwork's shotty at best.
Oh. "Hammer don't need
no tips. baby."
Sound like you know your boxin'.
- You fight?
- Used to.
I'm a little rusty.
- Yeah. me too.
- Oh. yeah?
Mm-mm. Caught you.
I thought that was you.
Been a minute since I've
seen you around the gym.
Yeah. well...
Aiden's always been asking
to come to your events.
So I wanted to make sure
it's a PG certified crowd.
I see you and Duke
have caught up.
- Not yet.
- Yeah.
Welcome back to London.
Good to see you.
Yeah. you too. Mrs. Marshall.
I'm gonna get going.
I've um...
seen all I need to see.
Before you go. I got a
gift for my little brother.
I'm sure you'd agree
with my father away.
now more than ever us Marshalls
need to stick together.
So. who am I workin' with.
big man?
One of our prospects.
Kareem Abdullah.
He's fighting on a
York Hall card tomorrow night.
All right.
I'll get started with him
on the heavy bag.
We're thinkin' bucket support.
I'm sure you'll do great.
They're here.
We should go upstairs.
Hey yo. you used
to fight. right?
- Yeah.
Amateur. NACs.
Yeah. same. Yeah.
It's good to see you
back on your feet. man.
I know you had your...
struggles. you know?
Listen. you don't
know shit about me.
Here you go.
No. no. that's yours.
There you go.
Here you go gentlemen.
That's- that's yours.
and that's yours.
Am I comin' through clearly?
We can hear you.
All right then.
let's not waste time.
I'm losing money by the minute.
We all are.
Let's hear Cebella out.
I would.
but I don't want to be around
the stench of Russian
cologne more than I have to.
Watch your
fuckin' mouth. Nadim.
Kiss my ass. Nikolai.
I just want to know
where's the product we paid for.
We wanted to ask
you lot the same.
You lot are the only other ones
that know about our shipments.
Listen. Sonny Jim.
I don't like being accused
of shit I didn't do.
None of us do.
If we don't get our
product or our money soon.
maybe we get our
product elsewhere...
My father's product and the
price he's willing to sell it at
protects you lot from the market
fluctuations your counterparts
in America and Europe
are currently struggling with.
That may be. little girl.
but your daddy's not here
to protect you.
When we find out
who's responsible.
they'll never earn
in London again.
Oi!
Don't be bringin' in no crumbs.
you hear me?
Mmhmm.
Just finished sweepin'
and I ain't doin' it again.
Quarter past eleven.
ain't there some old hag waitin'
for you to talk her ear off?
I'm tryin' to talk
more than her ear off.
if you know what I mean.
Mmm. Yeah.
Where's the Duke anyway.
I got a present for him.
I ain't his damn secretary.
how the hell would I know?
Oh. you don't seem too happy
the Duke's back.
Yeah. well.
I don't like surprises.
It's not a surprise
though. is he. he's your son.
Why the hell are you
so invested?
Snoopin' around here
lookin' for him.
I ain't really ever had
a family 'cept you.
Duke. and Calvin. and...
pfft. now I get another chance.
Yeah. I hear you kid.
But Duke ain't the same
anymore.
Gettin' odd packages
from Mexico of all places.
writin' down addresses.
Look. I'll check on him.
Where's this address that
you say he wrote down?
It's in there somewhere.
And then. Oi. get out of here.
- Yeah. yeah.
- Shops closed. yeah?
- I'll see ya later Gazzer. yeah?
- Yeah. see ya later.
Zeek and CeCe just had
an emergency meeting
with their entire network.
That hit has got
their cages rattled.
Yeah. so?
That was the plan.
Yeah look. about that.
I know what was planned but.
I looked into everyone's eyes.
Russians are wrong for this.
We need to target the Albanians.
We're not changing the plan
just 'cause you looked
in their eyes.
This isn't one
of your boxing matches.
Yeah. it is.
But when you're in a fight
and the gameplans not working.
what do you do?
Well. you got to be adaptable
to what our opponent does.
that's how we stay
one step ahead.
How we make 'em suffer.
Nikolai...
all right. he was pissed about
his lost product. right?
But he was respectful.
understanding even.
Nadim though...
now he didn't hold back
his anger.
Especially about Zeek
and CeCe running things.
We frame the Albanians. and
the Marshalls will believe it.
They run the stolen car market
in London.
Move 'em out the city once
a month in shipping containers.
There's one leaving tonight.
We leave now.
we can stash the drugs there.
I'll head out back.
start prepping the kit.
Hey. don't fuckin' move!
And step away from the knife!
It was you who
hit the warehouse.
All right. just...
Zeek and CeCe were
right not to trust you.
Hey...
they'll be happy
when I get rid of you.
Listen to me. man...
Listen to me. listen to me.
You need to start askin'
yourself
some really tough questions.
Like do I really have what
it takes to do this?
Am I a killer?
Duke!
Fuck's sake...
Jay...
- No. fuck that.
- I can explain.
Fuck that mate.
I can explain.
Who the hell is this?
What's goin' on here Duke?
What the fuck...
Shut the fuck up. man...
And who's this guy?!
The son of a bitch
has a recording device.
What the fuck is this?
You and him working together?
- No! No!
- Hey. whoa. whoa. whoa.
Hey. hey. hey. hey.
- Why should I believe you?
- 'Cause he's with me.
Well then he's not
goin' anywhere.
None of us are
until I figure out
what's goin' on here.
If not?
He's dead.
And so are you. Duke.
Do you want subtitles for any video?
-=[ ai.OpenSubtitles.com ]=-